Adeleye Oreoluwa

Front end Developer

Profile

I am a well-seasoned and experienced front-end engineer who can create stunning, user-friendly web pages. Proficient in an assortment of technologies, including HTML, CSS, Javascript, Tailwind, Bootstrap React JS, GIT and MongoDB. I am able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Employment History

Frontend engineer at RCCG junior church, Lagos

August 2022 — January 2023

- Building and maintenance of the front-end for a set of web pages required for operation and registration processes
- Edited existing web-pages
- Contributed to writing a Front-end guide for beginners.
- Mentoring and tutoring individuals interested in Front-end web development
- Continually worked to enhance my set of communication skills and strategies.

Frontend Engineer at NFT mafia, Remote

June 2022 — Present

- Development and maintenance of the official NFT mafia website.
- Built the back end for the sign-up feature of the website.
- Working in collaboration with UI/UX designers and Back-end engineers.
- Improved my team playing and problem solving skill.

Frontend Web dev at Beingsart NFT, Remote

March 2023 — Present

- Development and maintenance of the official Beingsart NFT website.
- Working alongside UI/UX designers and Backend engineers to maintain and build web pages and features for unstaking.

Education

frontend web development, Future Academy Africa, Remote

August 2022 — July 2023

• Intensive training on HTML CSS and JS.

Internships

React Developer at SideHustle, Remote

August 2022 — September 2022

 Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations.

Details

Lagos Nigeria 08160801541

orepaul12@@gmail.com

Links

Personal Portfolio

Skills

HTML & CSS

Node.js

MongoDB

Bootstrap

Git

jQuery

React

JavaScript

Animation

Hobbies

Gaming, writing Codes, Thinking